slystart.com 2013-02-18

# Privacy Policy Free Business Website Directory Listing

This Privacy Policy covers the SlyStart  Directory treatment of personal information that is recorded when you submit your site for inclusion in our database. Our privacy policy does not apply to the practices of other companies advertised, or otherwise listed, on theSlyStart  Directory web site, nor does it extend to people that SlyStart  Directory does not employ or manage. 

**Information Collection and Use**

SlyStart   Directory offers Free Basic Listings and Paid Express Listings. The information we collect is dependent on your needs. 

For Basic Listings, the only information collected is Name, Email Address, URL, Password and Descriptive Information for the Listing. Additional information is collected for Express Listings. 

Your use of SlyStart  Directory services (basic or express listing of your web site or sites) constitutes a business relationship wherein we provide a promotion service for your web site(s). In exchange, New Web Directory reserves the right to use the contact information collected during site submission to deliver notices regarding changes or updates to our service, to provide you with a free web site monitoring account (FreeWebMonitoring), to inform you of additions to the GreenWave Online Network of web sites, or to send announcements and carefully screened offers and information from our partners. 

With the exception of auto-response messages which are sent at the time of site submission and which contain important confirmation details regarding your site listing, you may remove yourself from any or all other notice and announcement mailings, at anytime using the unsubscribe methods provided in those mailings. In addition, you may cancel your free web site monitoring account at anytime. Any mailing received from our company is clearly identified and includes at least 2 methods to remove yourself from future mailings. Should you encounter problems in this regard, contact: inquiry[at]SlyStart .com. Our turnaround time for responding to unsubscribe requests is generally 24 hours. 

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

SlyStart  Directory maintains your email address and other pertinent personal information, provided at the time of your site submission, on the premises. SlyStart  Directory allows carefully screened vendors the opportunity to send you offers and information that we have deemed may be of value to you. You may opt-in or out of this feature at any time. 

**Cookies**

At this time, Cookies are not used on the SlyStart  Directory site. 

**Security**

Your personal information is stored in a protected directory. Access is restricted to SlyStart  Directory staff. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

SlyStart  Directory may amend this policy from time to time. If significant changes are made in the way your personal information is used, we will post a prominent announcement on our site notifying you of the change. 

**Questions or Suggestions**

Questions or suggestions may be sent to: inquiry[at]slystart.com 

|   
---|---
